24小时
第三季  第13集
前情提要
大卫 我相信你能连任
David, I still believe in your presidency.
如果艾伦·米利肯威胁到你领导国家的能力
And, if Alan Milliken is threatening your ability to lead this country,
我会阻止他
he will be stopped.
12年前 米利肯开车撞死了你女儿?
Milliken was driving the car that hit and killed your daughter 12 years ago?
对 我亲眼目睹的
Yeah. I saw Milliken driving the car that night.
凯利是唯一一个目击者
Kelly was the only one who saw it.
米利肯的人封了他的口
Then Milliken's people got to him.
-愿意宣誓作证吗?  -对
-He'll swear to this?  -Yes.
凯利先生?
Mr. Kelly?
-那是什么?   -一个婴儿
-What is that?  -It's a baby.
是 我知道那是个婴儿 金
Yeah, I can see that it's a baby, Kim.
是谁的孩子?
Whose baby is it?
-克萝伊的 -克萝伊没有孩子
-Chloe's.  -Chloe doesn't have a baby.
亚当刚和我说你不是这孩子的母亲
Adam just told me you're not the mother of this child.
坦白说 我认为她有幻想症
Frankly, I think she's delusional.
办公室里只有他能够过滤
She's the only one in this office capable of filtering audio streams
蔡斯发给我们的音频
that chase is sending us.
如果克萝伊不稳定...
If Chloe is unstable...
现在我们没有别的选择
We don't have an alternative right now.
我们必须让她继续工作
We have got to keep her in place.
阿马多尔15分钟后到这
Amador will be here in 15 minutes.
确定他带了病毒
Confirm that he has the virus,
给他钱 然后把病毒带回来给我们
give him his money, and bring the virus back to us.
干得好
Good job.
你对我没有任何价值了
I don't need you anymore.
他要杀了他 特种部队来不及赶到那里
He's going to kill him. Delta team's not going to get there in time.
拉姆 我们有个协议
Ramon, we had a deal.
-托尼特种部队来了  -蔡斯!
-Chase!  -Tony, delta's here.
我们只想要病毒
All we want is the virus.
把瓶子慢慢的放下来
Just put the cylinder down slowly.
趴下!
Get down!
我们没有拿到病毒!
We do not have the virus!
拉姆拿到的瓶子里装了炸弹
The cylinder Ramon was carrying was rigged with a bomb.
阿马多尔肯定调了包 我们跟踪得到他的位置吗?
Amador must have switched it. Do we have a position on him?
特种部队跟着他 杰克
Delta has a team on him, Jack.
他跑不远的
He won't get far.
举起双手!
Hands in the air!
趴到地上
Get on the ground.
杰克 阿马多尔伏击了特种3号部队
Jack, Amador ambushed Delta 3.
-那只是个圈套  -找到他的位置吗?
-It was a setup.  -What about his position?
伏击开始的时候我们就失去信号了
We lost the signal once the ambush happened.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
特种3号部队全军覆没
Delta 3's been taken out.
他们失去了阿马多尔的踪迹
They don't have a position on Amador.
-你想怎么做?  -我们必须找到尼娜
-What do you want to do?  -We've got to find Nina.
-我是鲍尔  -杰克?
-Jack?  -This is Bauer.
我发现在小路旁有亮光 是你吗?
I have an area lit up past the fire road. Is that you?
不是
Negative.
-我过去看看  -小心
-I'll check it out.  -Be careful.
不许动
Stop right there.
放下枪
Drop your gun.
放下!
Drop it!
双手抱头
Get your hands on your head.
你和杰克在用对讲机联系?
You on a two-way with Jack?
是的
Yeah.
发送代码6给他
Give him a code six.
我得把手放到口袋里
I'm going to reach in my bag,
才能把对讲机拿出来
and I'm going to pull out a two-way.
慢慢地
Slowly.
杰克?
Jack?
在?
Yeah?
代码6
I'm code six.
你看到的亮光是怎么回事?
What about the light you saw?
没事
It was nothing.
关掉 不是待机
Off. Not standby.
扔掉它
Throw it over here.
还有谁和你在一起?
Who else is on the grid with you?
-就我和杰克  -你说谎
-Just me and Jack.  -You're lying.
我看到了特种部队
I saw a delta team.
-他们往北了  -那阿马多尔呢?
-They went north.  -What about Amador?
他带着病毒逃跑了
He escaped with the virus.
他骗了所有人
He ripped off everybody.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
好吧
All right.
往山下走
Move down the hill.
-我们去哪里?  -走就是了
-Where we going?  -Just walk.
你还好吧?
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
联系特种部队
Contact delta.
告诉他们在机场和我们会和
Tell them to meet us at the airfield.
你准备怎么处理她 杰克?
What are you going to do to her, Jack?
-审问她  -不他不会的
-Interrogate her.  -No, he's not.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
蔡斯 请你
Chase, please.
相信我
Just trust me.
我会在机场和你会和
I'll meet you at the airfield.
杰克 阿马多尔手里仍旧有病毒
Jack, Amador still has the virus.
我可以帮你跟踪他
I can help you track him.
他选择这个镇的原因 是因为这里离边境很近
The only reason he chose this town is because it's close to the border.
他要回洛杉矶
He needs to get back to Los Angeles.
当他到了 他会和某人见面
Once he does, he's going to meet somebody,
交付病毒 然后消失
unload the virus, and disappear.
我可以帮你找到他
I can help you find him.
杰克 我不想死
Jack, I don't want to die.
让我帮你找到他
Let me help you find him.
我可以帮到你
I can help you.
-反恐局  -我是杰克鲍尔
-CTU.  -This is Jack Bauer.
帮我接通阿尔梅达
Patch me through to Almeida.
阿尔梅达.
Almeida
我活捉了尼娜·迈尔斯
I've got Nina Myers alive.
有阿马多尔的消息吗?
Any sign of Amador?
没有 在他伏击特种部队后就没有消息了
No. Not since he ambushed the delta team.
等卫星经过那里 我们会再扫描一遍的
Once the satellite comes around, we'll do a sweep.
尼娜说他前往洛杉矶了
Nina says he's headed to Los Angeles.
你相信她?
You believe her?
我认为她知道些事情 她想做个交易
I think she knows something. She wants to cut a deal.
我们会把她带回反恐局
We got to bring her back to CTU.
好的 我来准备一架飞机
Okay. I'll get a delta plane ready.
明白
Copy that.
起来... 慢慢地
Get up... slowly.
托尼 我要协调太多信息了
Tony, I'm coordinating too many comms.
我想把一些转给亚当小组
I need to offload some of it to Adam's group.
你都收到了?
You have everything?
是的
Yeah.
听着 克萝伊
Look, Chloe,
你需要和查佩尔谈谈
you need to go talk to Chappelle.
谈什么?
For what?
你心里明白
You know what for.
-你把日志更新了吗?  -金鲍尔
-Kim Bauer.  -Did you get a chance to update the logs?
大部分更新了 我爸爸和蔡斯发生了什么事?
Most of them. Look, what's going on with my dad and Chase?
这就是我要告诉你的
That's why I called.
他们正在返回洛杉矶
They're headed back to Los Angeles.
他们跟丢了阿马多尔 现在我们正在找他
They lost Amador. We're looking for him now.
那尼娜呢?
What about Nina?
她们带着尼娜一起回来
They're bringing her back with them.
谢谢你 托尼
Thank you, Tony.
好吧 你都明白了
Right. You got it.
我没别的要求 但事情得分轻重缓急 是吧?
I'd love nothing more, but we have to prioritize, don't we?
我了解
I understand.
好的
All right.
好 就这样 我要挂了
Yeah. All right. I got to go.
托尼说你想和我谈谈 我来了
Tony said you wanted to talk to me. Here I am.
请坐
Sit down.
如果你想和我聊婴儿的事 那么你是在浪费时间
If you want me to talk about the baby, you're wasting your time
因为我不会说什么的
because I'm not going to talk about her.
那么 请坐
So, sit down.
告诉我到底发生了什么事?
Tell me what the hell is going on.
什么?
What?
好吧
All right.
一开始 你告诉我们这是你的孩子
First, you told us the baby was yours.
我们发现这是个谎言
We found out that was a lie.
然后你又说 你和你的男朋友
Then you tell us you and your boyfriend
把孩子接了过来 因为他在生母那边受了虐待
took it from its mother because the baby was being abused.
我确实说过这话 但是我现在要更正我说的
I did say that, and I'd like to correct that right now.
我没有男朋友
I don't have a boyfriend.
你让我们没办法相信你
You're unbelievable.
这孩子是谁的?
Who does the baby belong to?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
你带了个未经授权的人进入这栋楼
You brought an unauthorized person into this building.
那违反了联邦法律的
That's a federal offense.
-那只不过是个婴儿  -我不在乎这个
-It's just a baby.  -I don't care who it is.
你违规了
You're in violation.
好吧 我违规了
Fine. I'm in violation.
这孩子到底是谁的 克萝伊?
Who does the baby belong to, Chloe?
你是不是想让我把孩子带到楼下的实验室
Do you want me to take it down to the lab
做血液测试来查出他的身份?
and run blood tests to get an I.D.?
我会这么做的
Because I will.
我不想再说任何有关这个孩子的事情了
I'm not going to talk any more about this baby.
这并不是因为我是一个多么恐怖的坏人
And it's not because I'm a horrible, evil person.
只是因为我不能这么做
It's just because I can't do it.
请不要在她身上使用针管
Just please don't start sticking needles in her.
-是的查佩尔先生  -艾琳?
-Eileen?  -Yes, Mr. Chappelle.
叫保安来
Send security in.
在我们为婴儿做血液测试时 我需要有人监视克萝伊
I want Chloe O'Brian under guard while we run some tests on the baby.
马上来 先生
Right away, sir.
反恐局的托尼·阿尔梅达刚刚通知我们
Tony Almeida from CTU has just informed us
他们没能在墨西哥成功收缴科迪利亚病毒
that they were unable to confiscate this Cordilla virus in Mexico.
我认为他们已经确认了卖家 并且包围了整个地区
I thought they located the seller and had the entire area surrounded.
这个卖家... 一个叫迈克尔 阿马多尔的卖家...
Well, this seller... a man named Michael Amador...
很显然 他从来没有打算放弃病毒
apparently, he never intended to give up the virus.
事实上这是一个精心策划的骗局
In fact, it was a well-planned rip-off
大卫 我们失去了6个人
David, we lost six men.
他们是特种部队的
Members of a delta team.
我们失去了一个三角洲小组
We lost a delta team.
这个阿马多尔... 他现在在哪?
This man Amador... where is he now?
最新情报表明阿马多尔带着病毒
Latest working theory is that Amador has this virus, and is
正返回洛杉矶
headed back here to Los Angeles.
来释放病毒吗?
To release it?
我们不知道 但是阿马多尔没有恐怖袭击的历史
We don't know, but Amador doesn't have a history of implementing terrorist strikes.
他是个让人捉摸不定的军火商
He's an arms dealer with no known ideology.
我们不知道他究竟要干什么
Bottom line is we just don't know what his intentions are.
抱歉打扰了 先生
Sorry to interrupt, sir.
我终于联络到了雪莉 帕默尔
I finally reached Sherry Palmer.
她现在在线吗?
Is she on the line now?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
这里继续 韦恩
Continue here, Wayne.
雪莉.
Sherry
大卫 很抱歉我没有联系你
David, I'm sorry I couldn't call you back.
我必须立刻离开凯利家
I had to leave Kelly's in a hurry.
我们通电话后 你是不是回去和他交谈过了?
Did you go back and talk to him after we spoke?
是这样的 当我回去的时候 他已经离开了
That's just it. When I got back there, he was gone.
离开了?
Gone?
你认为他逃跑了吗?
You think he ran?
不 我不这么认为
No, I don't,
因为他已经准备好站出来对抗米利肯
because he was more than ready and willing to come forward against Milliken.
但是显然有人先我们一步找到了他
But someone obviously got to him first.
你有没有看到任何人?
But you didn't see anyone?
没有 我跑回车上然后离开了这
No. I ran back to my car and got out of there.
我有点 呃...
I was, uh...
我在那里感到很害怕大卫
I was pretty scared there, David.
米利肯肯定盯着你呢
Milliken must be on to you.
立刻回来
Get back here as soon as you can.
你在外面不安全
It's not safe for you out there anymore.
我必须先做一些事
I really need to do something first.
什么事?
What?
我必须去见朱莉娅 米利肯
I've gotta go see Julia Milliken.
不 不 我不希望今晚你去任何靠近她或艾伦的地方
No, no. I don't want you to go anywhere near her or Alan tonight.
我必须去 大卫
I have to, David.
艾伦·米利肯动作很快 绑架了...
Alan Milliken had to move fast in order to kidnap...
也许已经杀了凯文 凯利
maybe even kill this Kevin Kelly guy.
我必须在他毁掉一切证据前找到它们
I've got to take advantage of that before he has time to cover his tracks.
雪莉,
Sherry
我不希望你和艾伦正面接触
I do not want you confronting Alan.
听我说 大卫
I told you, David,
我只是去和朱莉娅谈谈
I'm just going to talk to Julia.
我保证 我会远离艾伦
I promise, I'll stay away from Alan.
-雪莉...  -大卫,
-Sherry...  -David
你让我来帮你的 对吧?
you asked me to help you, right?
拜托
Please,
让我这么做吧
let me do that.
那边发生了什么事?
What happened back there?
她想帮我们找到阿马多尔
She wants to help us find Amador.
探员鲍尔 麦克·墨菲 特种4号部队
Agent Bauer, Mike Murphy, Delta 4.
海军提供了一架C-130
The navy was good enough to reroute a C-130.
代我向他们致谢
Tell them we said thank you.
我们将带你和这个囚犯去洛杉矶
We're going to take you and the prisoner back to Los Angeles.
阿马多尔那边有什么动静吗?
Any movement on Amador?
没有 空军一直在监视整个地区
No. Air tactical's been monitoring the entire area.
至今 没什么消息
So far, nothing.
杰克 你确定你要离开?
Jack, you sure you want to leave?
铐住她
Secure her.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
阿马多尔已经跑了
Amador's already gone.
他计划好了一切
He's planned this thing well.
我们需要找到谁想要这个病毒
We need to find who wants the virus,
和他们何时何地会释放这病毒
and where and when they're going to release it.
我们必须走了 我们必须离开了
We need to go now. We need to leave.
-你好  -马库斯是我
-Hello.  -Marcus, it's me.
你在哪?
Where are you?
我一个小时后到
I'll be there in an hour.
拿到病毒了没?
Got the virus?
是的
Yes.
准备好一切
Just be ready.
我会的
I will be.
你好?
Hello?
朱莉娅 我快到了
Julia, I'm almost there.
艾伦现在在哪?
Where is Alan now?
-他在房间里  -他睡了吗?
-He's in his room.  -Is he asleep?
没有 他刚去接电话了
No. He just got off the phone with someone.
你知道是谁的电话吗?
Do you know who he was talking to?
-你听到名字了吗?  -没有没有
-Did you hear a name?  -No. No.
我怎么能在他不察觉的情况下见到你?
How do I get to you without him knowing?
大门的密码是4132
The gate code is 4132.
把车停在门侧 然后走过服务区的走廊
Park off to the side, then walk up to the service porch.
-我会在那  -好的
-I'll be there.  -All right,
再说一遍密码?
what's that number again?
4132.
好的 那里有监视器吗?
Okay. Are there any security cameras?
有
Yes.
确定他们关闭了
Then make sure they're disabled.
雪莉 我不确定我是不是可以
Sherry, I don't know if I can.
想个办法朱莉娅
Find a way, Julia.
我会在几分钟后到
I'll be there in a few minutes.
... 在选票中领先
... is ahead in the polls and gaining favor
受到美国人的青睐
with the American people.
至于帕默尔总统...
As for President Palmer...
你还没睡啊?
You're up late.
肯从新加坡打来
Ken called from Singapore.
他还是不会算时差
He still hasn't figured out how to calculate the time difference.
你自己睡吧
You should be in bed yourself.
我会的
I will.
我刚喝了点茶
I just put on some tea.
让我的胃舒服点
I'd like to settle my stomach.
随你
All right, then.
好吧
All right.
晚安
Good night.
朱莉娅.
Julia
我知道你的情感和尊严受到侮辱
I know you felt demeaned earlier,
但那些都过去了
but that's behind us now.
我知道
I know it is.
我让你活着 告诉我知道什么
I let you live, tell me what you know.
每次阿马多尔在西岸做生意
Anytime Amador does business on the west coast,
他总是通过一个叫阿尔弗斯的人洗钱的
he washes his deal through a man named Alvers.
阿尔弗斯?
Alvers?
他的名字呢?
What's his first name?
我只知道叫阿尔弗斯 可能是姓也可能是名
All I know is Alvers. It could be a first or a last name.
阿马多尔怎么联系阿尔弗斯?
How does Amador contact this Alvers?
我不知道 我从没见过他
I don't know. I've never met him.
但是在我们的交易前我查过阿马多尔
But I did check out Amador before our deal,
我不只一次看到阿尔弗斯这个名字
and I kept coming across the name Alvers.
他是阿马多尔之前很多交易的联系人
He was a connector to a lot of his past deals, and
洛杉矶就是交易的中间站
Los Angeles was always the hub.
蔡斯 你在和反恐局通话
Chase, you on with CTU?
是的 是托尼
Yeah. It's Tony.
告诉他我想和他通话
Tell him I want to speak to him.
托尼 杰克有话和你说
Tony, Jack wants to talk to you.
-嘿杰克  -托尼
-Tony.  -Hey, Jack.
我想让你查一个叫阿尔弗斯的人
I want you to run a check on the name Alvers.
查找这个名字和迈克尔 阿马多尔的所有联系
Cross-reference it with everything you've got on Michael Amador.
就这些吗?
Is that it?
-是的  -只是名字...
-Yeah.  -Just the name...
阿尔弗斯. A-I-v-e-r-s.
Alvers A-I-v-e-r-s
你从尼娜得到的?
You got this from Nina?
是的
Yeah.
好的 我来查 查好我会联系你
All right, I'll work it up, I'll get back to you.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
留着吧
Keep it.
-手怎么样了?  -别担心会好的
-How's the hand?  -Don't worry about it, it's fine.
听着 蔡斯 我们今天经历了很多
Look, Chase, you and I have been through a lot today.
为什么我们不忘记那些 然后好好工作呢
Why don't we try and move past it and do our job.
你不信任我 杰克
You don't trust me, Jack.
为什么你不告诉我你和赫克托的交易?
Why didn't you tell me about your deal with Hector?
这只是盖尔 托尼和我之间的秘密
It couldn't go beyond Gael, Tony and myself.
这是我唯一知道我可以保密的办法
That's the only way I knew I could contain it.
那你认为 我不应该追踪你和拉姆吗?
And what did you think, that I wasn't going to come after you and Ramon?
我不知道是该保护你还是杀你
I didn't know whether to save you or kill you.
我希望你能听从我的命令
I expected you to follow my orders.
但是如果是我的话 也许我也会这么做的
But I probably would have done the same thing myself.
你用抢顶着我的头...
You put a gun to my head...
你扣动了扳机
and you pulled the trigger.
我只是做了个判断拉姆·萨拉扎不会
I made a judgment call that Ramon Salazar would not
给我有子弹的武器... 他只是想试探我
give me a loaded weapon... that he was testing me.
如果上了子弹呢?
And if it was loaded?
那怎么样呢?
Then what?
我必须完成我的任务
I'd have finished my mission.
蔡斯 听我说
Chase, listen to me.
你干这行很久了 你必须做选择
You do this job long enough, you're going to have to make choices,
事情结束前
and you don't know you've made the right one
你不知道你是不是选对了
until the whole scenario plays itself out.
现在唯一重要的事是 如果我们不阻止病毒的散播
Right now the only thing that matters is if we don't stop this virus,
这个世界会被永久的改变
the world as we know it will change forever.
就是这个事实 仅仅是这个事实
And that fact, and that fact alone
你所要考虑的就是这个事实 而你也是知道的
is the only thing that you have to keep in the front of your mind, and you know that.
是的
Yeah.
对
你为什么不继续审问她?
Why don't you keep pressing her?
她可能还没有把所有的事告诉你
She probably hasn't told you everything.
对 她可能还没全说出来
No, she probably hasn't.
我们还是等一下
We're going to have to wait.
确定阿尔弗斯的真伪
Make sure Alvers is a real lead.
在数据库里找到了一千多个阿尔弗斯
Over a thousand Alvers showed up in the Langley database.
我做了背景调查 并且结合了阿马多尔的信息
I did background checks and consistency-refs with Amador.
这是唯一一个符合的
This is the only one that red flagged.
马库斯 阿尔弗斯.
Marcus Alvers
出生于奥地利 后来搬到英国
Born in Austria, moved to England.
在剑桥学习生物学时和阿马多尔认识
Met Amador in Cambridge where Alvers was studying biology.
在1994年 他们被怀疑生产武器级别的炭症病毒
In 1994, they were suspected of manufacturing weapons-grade anthrax,
但是没有确切证据
but there was no hard evidence.
听起来像是我们要找的人
Sounds like this is our guy.
是的 虽然还只是粗略结果
Yeah, the dossier's sketchy,
但是阿尔弗斯和阿马多尔在过去几年里接触了很多次
but Alvers and Amador have definitely crossed paths over the years.
情报局也有一些文件
CIA had these on file.
在过去3年中 有14次阿尔弗斯和阿马多尔短暂的目击记录
Over the past three years, there have been 14 sightings of Alvers and Amador together
在欧洲和东非
throughout Europe and east Africa.
好的 那我们怎么找到阿尔弗斯?
All right, so how do we find Alvers?
我们有些线索 我们还得继续找
We have some threads. We need to work them all up.
我们需要到部里调人手来帮忙
We're going to need manpower from Division.
米歇尔 你去帮忙
Michelle, hook them up.
鲍尔.
Bauer
你好 杰克 我们找到个符合的阿尔弗斯
Yeah, Jack, we got a match on Alvers.
我们现在去找到他
Now we got to find him.
需要花点时间
It's going to take some time.
好的 我看看从中我们能发现什么
Okay, I'll see what we can do from here.
找到了
We're on.
看起来你给我们的阿尔弗斯的信息是真实的
Looks like the information you gave us on Alvers is real.
当然是真的
Of course it is.
反恐局不可能在他见阿马多尔前找到他
CTU is not going to find him before his meeting with Amador.
但是我可以帮你
But I can help you.
怎么帮?
How?
我还知道点别的
I know a little more than I said I did.
听着 没有时间为这协议签章
Look, I know there's no time for a signed deal,
因此我打算相信你会在司法部在这个案子上帮助我
so I'm going to trust you to support my case with the Department of Justice
如果我帮你找到病毒
if I help you secure this virus.
我答应了
You've got my word.
这个男人的全名叫马库斯 弗莱德rick 阿尔弗斯
The man's name is Marcus Fredrick Alvers.
他是个业余的生物学家 并且打算成为一个恐怖分子
He's an amateur biologist and wanna-be terrorist.
在维也纳和洛杉矶都闹过事 并在伦敦待了2年
Raised hell from Vienna to Los Angeles, with a two-year stop in London.
我有他的电话
I have a number for him.
你必须先拨打一串特殊号码
You have to dial a Felco prefix first,
之后你能通过网络电话联系上他
and then you can reach him through an internet socket.
把电话给我
Give me the cold line.
号码是?
What's the number?
1-7-7-5-5-3-1.
1-7-7-5-5-3-1
你会听到忙音 但是不要挂
You're going to get a fast busy signal, but don't hang up.
我听到忙音了
I've got the busy signal.
按9并且按住3秒
Hit nine and hold it for three seconds.
听到嘟声了?
Do you get a tone?
是 我听到了
Yeah, I've got a tone.
拨 95731*6
Hit 95731*6.
是振铃
It's ringing.
当振铃停止后 你会听到一系列数字
When the ringing stops, you're going to get a series of numbers...
那就是你的IP地址
that's your IP address.
停止振铃了
It stopped ringing.
我没有听到任何号码
I'm not getting any numbers.
没事的 等一下
That's okay. Just wait.
喂?
Yeah?
技术室所以电脑都发生了问题
The tech room is spiking all over the place.
你能从你那边重启电脑吗?
Can you reset it from there?
我不知道 我马上回你电话
I don't know. I'll have to get back to you.
亚当 发生什么事了? 我的系统上锁了
Adam, what's going on? My system's locked.
技术部门
Division. Tech.
-Matt我是反恐局的亚当  -是亚当听着
-Matt, it's Adam at CTU.  -Yeah, Adam, look.
怎么回事 电缆出了问题
We don't know what's going on. Our cable's blocked up here.
我尽快给你回电
I'll get back to you.
不用再重播了 杰克 一次足够了
Don't need to dial it again, Jack. Once was enough.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你刚刚激活了一个切断局里网络连接的病毒
You just triggered a worm that's going to bring down agency connectivity.
天啊 你做了什么?
My god, what have you done?
你到底做了什么?!
What have you done?!
你整个反恐怖分子的网络被堵塞了
Until I say otherwise, your entire anti-terrorist computer network is jammed.
听着!
Listen up!
我们的计算机系统感染了一种自我繁殖的程序
We got some kind self-propagating code leaking into the system!
关闭你们的网络连接 保存尽可能多的程序!
Shut down your sockets, save everything you can!
我们必须找出这个东西的来源
We got to find where this thing came from.
你什么意思 尼娜做的吗?
What do you mean, Nina did this?
她工作时 是对我们的系统是最了解的人
She knew our system better than anyone when she worked there.
她把一个病毒嵌入了一个驱动
She embedded a worm into a part of the driver
她知道这个驱动不会被升级
that she knew we'd never upgrade.
-这是她告诉你的?  -是的
-She told you this?  -Yes.
她想要什么?
What does she want?
我不知道 我们很快会弄明白的
I don't know. We're gonna find out soon enough.
听着 你那得人能解决这问题吗?
Look, can your people stop this thing?
我们在尽全力 杰克
We're doing our best, Jack.
把克萝伊从我的小组里调出来
Pull Chloe out of my sector.
她比任何人都了解网络
She knows the network better than anyone.
这个有些麻烦
It's going to be a problem.
-她被暂停工作了  -你在说什么?为什么?
-She's been asked to step aside.  -What are you talking about? Why?
说来话长 杰克
It's a long story, Jack.
托尼 现在不是让克萝伊暂停工作地时候
Tony, this is not the time to take Chloe out of play.
你和我一样明白多少恐怖分子
You know as well as I do how many terrorist cells try to
想攻击我们的系统
hack into our system every day.
这个病毒毁掉了我们的防火墙
This thing eats through our firewalls,
我们的情报员正在成为目标
we're gonna have agents as targets by morning.
好吧 尼娜怎么样?
All right. What about Nina?
你有办法让她告诉我们怎么消除这个病毒吗?
Is there any way you can get her to tell us how to neutralize this thing?
我正在努力 我等会电话你
I'll start working on it. I'll get back to you.
好的
All right.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
让飞机掉头 返回墨西哥
Turn the plane around and head back to Mexico.
只要你做了 我就减缓病毒散播的速度
Once you do, I'll slow down the spread of the worm.
当我们到达并且我平安离开 我会给你最终的杀毒程序
When we land and I'm safely away, I'll give you the final kill code.
这是不可能的
That will never happen.
多少恐怖组织一直在等着这个机会?
How many terrorist cells are waiting for a window like this?
几百个?
A couple hundred?
30分钟内 他们会从世界各地读取反恐局的内部文件
In 30 minutes, they'll all have access to CTU files everywhere.
你不会想让那个发生的
You don't want that to happen.
掉转飞机
Turn the plane around.
你是在假设我们的人无法杀掉这个病毒
You're assuming our people can't stop this thing.
我请你试一试
I invite you to try.
相信我 瑞恩 我知道
Believe me, Ryan, I know.
现在克萝伊是唯一一个了解这个部分
Right now, Chloe's the only person who knows enough about this section
阻止病毒扩散的人
of code to stop the worm.
好吧
Fine.
Steve 你可以走了
Steve, you can go.
谢谢 先生
Yes, sir.
发生什么事了?
What's happening?
现在有个病毒在侵蚀我们的网络
There's a worm eating through our network.
尼娜·迈尔斯真通过某种方法远程激活了它
Nina Myers somehow managed to launch it remotely, and
它正在内部疯狂繁衍
it's running rampant in the kernel.
托尼说你可以阻止 是吗?
Tony says you can stop it. Is that correct?
是的 如果它还没有毁掉太多的网络数据
Yeah, if it hasn't destroyed too much of the routing data.
好的 去做吧
Good. Do it.
亚当 你有关掉所有的网关吗?
Adam, did you close all the gateways?
-是的  -重新打开12和14端口
-Yeah.  -Reopen 12 and 14.
为什么?
What for?
病毒就不会被传播到余下的系统 我们只有对不核心的就可以了
They won't leak into the rest of the system, and they get us to the kernel.
道尔顿 检查网络所有结点的连接状态
Dalton, start pinging the nodes in the I.T.
当数据包不再丢失 终止该线程
When you stop getting packet loss, freeze the process.
-我去技术室  -好的
-I'll be in the tech room.  -All right.
你来这里我感到很不舒服 雪莉
I'm really not comfortable with you being here, Sherry.
为什么你不直接告诉我你要什么?
So why don't you just tell me what you want?
噢 别这样 朱莉娅
Oh, come on, Julia.
我之前告诉过你
I told you earlier.
我知道你的婚姻
I know about your marriage.
我了解你的生活
I know about your life.
我知道你更愿意和你所爱的人一起生活
I know that you'd rather be with the man that you love,
但你现在和艾伦在一起因为他的钱和安全感
but you stay with Alan because of his money and the security.
我不需要一个解剖我的精神病医生
I don't need a drive-through shrink,
除非你来这有什么真正的原因...
so unless you have some real reason to be here...
那么谋杀呢?
How about murder?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
一个叫凯文 凯利的男人
A man named Kevin Kelly
有一些针对艾伦的资料可以致他于死地
has information on Alan that could hurt him very badly.
一个小时前
An hour ago,
凯利消失了
Kelly disappeared.
-消失了?  -他有可能被杀害了
-Disappeared?  -It's possible he was killed.
-你认为是艾伦干的?  -噢亲爱的我知道是艾伦干的
-And you think Alan is involved?  -Oh, sweetie, I know Alan is involved.
你可以帮我证实这个
And you're going to help me prove it.
即使我可以那么做
Even if I could do that,
-为什么我要帮你?  -因为这是你离开这里的票啊
-why would I?  -Because it's your ticket out of here.
如果艾伦入狱
If Alan goes to prison,
你得到一切 朱莉娅
you get everything, Julia.
你想要我做什么?
What would you need me to do?
好的 首先
Okay, first,
我要你找出最近2小时 他打出的所有电话号码
I need you to find out what phone calls he's made in the past two hours.
艾伦总是关门打电话的
Alan makes all his phone calls behind closed doors.
-他是用家里的电话吗?  -他自己的手机
-Does he use the house phone?  -His cell.
他总是带着手机的 这样他坐轮椅时会方便很多
He usually keeps it with him. It makes things a lot easier with his wheelchair.
手机现在在哪?
Where's the cell phone now?
在他房间
In his room.
我需要你拿到那个手机
I need you to get that phone.
不可能 艾伦刚睡
No. Alan just went to bed.
我还不确定他是不是睡着了
I'm not even sure he's asleep yet.
那你为什么不去看看呢?
Then why don't you find out?
我不能
I can't.
你难道不想离开他?
Don't you want to be free of him?
我害怕
I'm afraid.
好吧 我不怕
Well, I'm not.
他卧室在哪?
Where's the bedroom?
将B节点的组许可设定为577
Set the group permission on the beta node to 577,
并设为沿树向下走的
and make it recursive, all the way down the tree.
我希望每个在C卷的人不要乱动 直到我彻底解决问题为止
I want anyone who's on the cipher volume to stay off until I'm done.
好的
Okay.
亚当那些网关都打开了吗?
Adam, are those gateways open?
是的 当然
Yeah, of course.
我正试图发出这个病毒的定义文件
I'm trying to seed a virus definition.
我希望你能做得到
I hope you have enough to go on.
我们过一分钟就知道了
We'll know in a minute.
干这个让我感到很难过 当我得知你和金在背后捅我一刀
It's sad that I have to do this, knowing that you and Kim stabbed me in the back.
那你让我怎么做 克萝伊?
What do you want me to do, Chloe?
你违反了规定 之后又到处说谎
You're breaking rules and then lying about it all over the place.
你告诉我应该怎么做
Tell me what you'd do.
我对我的同事有更多的信任
I'd have more faith in my fellow worker.
不 你必须遵守制度
No, you'd follow protocol.
你是所有人里违反规定最严重的
You're the biggest rule freak of anyone.
我认为我违反规定是正确的
I think I've done a pretty good job at breaking the rules,
试图保护我的朋友和那个孩子 不是吗?
trying to protect a friend and that baby, wouldn't you say?
什么朋友?
What friend?
结束了
It's done.
见鬼
Damn it!
没用
It didn't work.
病毒的传播加速了?
The worm's speeding up!
怎么可能?
How is that possible?
我们肯定激活了什么东西
We must have triggered something.
打开1号和4号
Open one and four.
这难道不会把核心暴露出去吗?
Won't that expose the kernel?
会 但我们别无选择
Yeah, but we have no choice.
去做吧!
Do it!
-0-7?  -不是 4-7
-0-7?  -No, 4-7.
是的 最后一个号码的区位号是206
Yes. And the last one on here has a 206 area code.
-华盛顿?  -是的 号码是555-0191
-Washington?  -Yeah, that's 555-0191.
-就这个?  -是的
-That's it?  -Yeah.
-收到  -好的
-All right.  -Okay.
噢 B瑞恩t
Oh, and Bryant,
-谢谢你了 -你还好吧?
-thank you so much.  -You okay?
恩 给我回电话
Yeah, just call me.
好的
All right.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我有个朋友能追踪艾伦打过的电话
I have someone who can track the calls that Alan made from this phone,
如果任何一个和凯利有关联
and if any of them can be connected to Kelly,
我们就有对付艾伦的证据了
we have evidence that we can use against Alan.
-我需要做什么?  -什么都不用做
-What should I do?  -Nothing.
绝对什么都不用做 只要回到床上
Absolutely nothing. Just go to bed,
对你而言
and as far as you're concerned,
这里什么事情都没有发生
nothing happened here.
朱莉娅 为什么你还不睡?
Julia, why aren't you in bed?
你和谁在说话?
And who are you talking to?
雪莉?
Sherry?
你好 艾伦
Hello, Alan.
朱莉娅 我对你太失望了
Julia, I'm disappointed in you.
我没让她来
I didn't ask her here.
但你让她进来了
But you let her in.
而且你拿了我的手机
And you took my cell phone as well.
不
No,
是我拿走手机的
I took the phone.
你认为你在做什么呢 雪莉?
So what do you think you're going to do, Sherry?
阻止我?
Stop me?
不可能的
That's not likely.
好吧
All right,
如果你想扯开了谈? 好的
you want to talk about this in the open? Fine.
凯文·凯利怎么了?
What happened to Kevin Kelly?
凯文·凯利...
Kevin Kelly...
名字听起来很耳熟
the name rings a bell.
当然了耳熟
well, it should ring a bell.
他就是看见你12年前开车撞死他女儿的人
He's the man that saw you run over his daughter and kill her 12 years ago.
就是你付了很多封口费的人
The man you paid a considerable amount of money to keep quiet.
也是你今晚让他消失了的人
And the man you made disappear tonight.
那么你为什么不再好好想想呢?
So why don't you chew on that a bit?
也许我们可以明天再聊
And maybe we can talk about it a little more tomorrow.
或者我们现在了结
Or we can end it now,
而你也能远离大卫了
and you can back off David.
-是的我是Beauer  -克萝伊找你
-Yeah, this is Bauer.  -Chloe O'Brian for you, sir.
好的 我把电话给她
Fine. Patch her through.
尼娜 我知道你所有的事
Nina, I've heard all about you.
我知道你做的事 而你为求生所做的事也让我很佩服
I know what you've done, and how you've managed to stay alive is impressive.
但是如果你再耍杰克一次
But if you try to play Jack one more time,
他会杀了你
he's going to kill you.
会这样吗?
Is that so?
会的
Yeah.
我把你放到扬声器上
I'm going to put you on speakerphone.
3分钟内 我们整个系统将被关掉
In about three minutes, our entire system's going to be down.
你想要什么的话 你最好现在告诉我怎样杀掉这个病毒
You want any leverage, you better start telling me how to stop this thing now.
病毒不会传播得那么快 杰克
It doesn't move that fast, Jack.
你错了 克萝伊 把它放到屏幕上
You're wrong. Chloe, put it up on the screen.
你已经没有什么时间来做交易了
You're running out of time here to cut a deal.
解释给她听 克萝伊
Explain it to her, Chloe.
当我尝试隔离东岸路由器时 病毒传播速度加快了3倍
When I try to separate the routers in the east coast, the worm speed tripled.
你是谁?
Who is this?
克萝伊·奥布莱恩 我的网络监视器已经打开了
Chloe O'Brian. My network monitor's up.
我该怎么做?
What do I do?
使用用户名 "CIS27A" 登陆
Log in with user I.D. "CIS27A."
现在询问安全级别
It's asking for a security level.
输入 空格和6
Hit escape six.
-就这样?  -是的
-That's it?  -Yes.
克萝伊 病毒停止了吗?
Chloe, did that stop it?
没有
No.
等一分钟
Wait a minute.
那个没有停止 但是减速了
It didn't stop it, but it's slowing down.
我们还有多少时间?
How much more time do we have?
我们的模拟显示还有20分钟
Our simulation says just over 20 minutes.
我给你回电话
I'll get back to you.
好的 我已经减速了
Okay, so I slowed it down.
你现在需要掉转飞机回墨西哥
Now you need to turn the plane around and head back to Mexico.
如果你不做的话 你们那些隐藏在世界各地的情报人员
If you don't, you can expect your undercover agents around the world
将在1个小时内被屠杀
to start dying within the hour.
尼娜 你要回洛杉矶
Nina, you're going back to Los Angeles.
你要帮我找到阿马多尔 之后你要回到狱中
You're going to help me find Amador, and then you're going to prison.
这就是将要发生的事
That's what's happening here.
我为你家做了那么多事 你却闯进我的房子?
You come into my house after everything I've done for your family?!
我让你孩子们的父亲成为了美国总统!
I've made your children's father the President of the united states!
等等 你所做的一切不只是为了我的孩子们
You wait a minute. Whatever you did to help David was not for the benefit of my children.
让我们打开天窗说亮话
Let's get that straight.
你只是个卑鄙小人 艾伦
You're just a small man, Alan,
一个用钱来控制他的朋友们的小人
who lords his money over his friends because that's all you have.
那就是你!
That's all you are!
为什么你老婆跑出去找别的男人?
Why do you think your wife had to go out and find another man?
-不要这样和我说话!  -因为你不是任何大人物!
-Don't you talk to me like this!  -Because you're not one!
如果不是因为钱 哪个正常的女人
Not one woman in her right mind would find you attractive
会看上你 艾伦
without your wealth, Alan.
那就是人们想从你身上得到的 那就是朱莉娅想从你那得到的
That's what people want from you. That's all Julia wants from you.
难到我要怕你吗?
And I'm supposed to be afraid of you?
你认为我怕你吗?
You think I'm scared of you?
你只不过是个小男孩 艾伦
You're just a little boy, Alan,
一个可怜的 骨瘦如柴的 有病的小男人!
a pathetic, scrawny, sickly little boy!
朱莉娅 我的药
Julia, my pills.
我的药
My pills.
不 不要
No, don't.
-你在做什么?  -不要
-What are you doing?  -Don't.
-不要  -雪莉.
-Sherry.  -Don't.
-这是你离开的机会  -朱莉娅!朱莉娅!
-Julia! Julia!  -This is your way out.
朱莉娅!
Julia!
好吧 我们不能呆在这 朱莉娅
All right, we can't stay here, Julia.
-我们杀了他  -不不没有人杀了他
-We killed him.  -No, no, no one killed him.
-我们看着他死的  -不都结束了朱莉娅
-We watched him die.  -No, it's over, Julia.
-我们看着...他死!  -都结束了!
-We watched... him die!  -It's over!
现在艾伦是一个有病的小人
Now Alan was a sick little man.
他病发而亡 当时身边没有人
And his weak body gave out. Nobody was around to help him.
而你 你在你的卧室
And you, you were in your bedroom.
明白吗?
Understand me?
你不再受他的控制了 甜心
You're free of him, sweetie.
这是你所要考虑的
That's all you need to think about.
但有件事你必须清楚
But there's one thing you're gonna have to be really clear about,
当警察来审问你的时候
when the authorities come around questioning you:
这是场意外
This was an accident.
-我做不到  -你没有选择
-I don't think I can do this.  -You don't have a choice.
除非你余生想在监狱里度过
Unless you want to spend the rest of your pretty little life in prison.
噢 上帝啊
Oh, god.
好了 你回到卧室去
All right, you go into your bedroom.
你在那里呆一个小时
You stay there for about an hour.
然后呢出来取一杯水
Then you're gonna come out for a glass of water,
然后你...
and then you're gonna...
你看到了尸体
you're gonna see the body.
这就是你的故事了
Now that's your story.
我电话谁?
Who do I call?
911.
这是你自然地反应 对不对?
That's what you would naturally do, right?
对 那你呢?
Okay. What about you?
不 不 你听好了
No, no, you listen.
你仔细听好了因为这个很关键
You listen real strong'cause this is very crucial.
如果任何人...
If anyone...
怀疑我来过这
suspects that I was here,
就会产生调查
there will be an investigation,
我们就都会进监狱
and both of us will go to prison.
我从来没来过
I was never here.
明白了吗?
You understand?
朱莉娅 你现在告诉我你明白我在说什么
Julia, you tell me right now that you understand what I'm saying.
我明白
I understand.
好的
Okay.
妈的 停止那个程序
Damn it. Stop that process,
更糟糕了
it's making it worse.
-克萝伊发生什么事了?  -我控制不了它
-Chloe, what's going on?  -I'm not getting it.
-要多少时间?  -我不知道
-What's it going to take?  -I don't know.
克萝伊 如果你停不了那个程序 我必须让杰克调转机头
Chloe, if you can't stop this worm, then I have to tell Jack to re-route that plane
满足尼娜的需求
to wherever Nina wants.
托尼 请让我工作
Tony, please let me work.
-是鲍尔  -杰克
-It's Bauer.  -Jack.
告诉我你的人有办法处理了
Tell me your people have got a handle on this thing.
我们要降落了
We're on final approach.
我们没有
We don't.
尼娜不打算把杀毒程序给我们
Nina's not gonna give us the kill code
除非我们把飞机飞回墨西哥
until we turn the plane around back to Mexico,
而我一点也不想那么做
and I have no intention of doing that.
我们没有选择
We don't have a choice.
告诉飞行员调转机头
Tell the pilot to re-route the plane now.
我们必须停止这个病毒
We have to do whatever it takes to stop this thing.
托尼 这不是个好主意...
Tony, that's not an alternative...
托尼.
Tony
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
当系统毁坏了
Once the damage is done,
你什么交易也别想了
you're not going to be able to cut a deal.
现在给我杀毒码
Give me the kill code now.
杰克.
Jack
什么?
What?
想想看
Think about it.
现在你必须满足她
You should give her what she wants right now.
那不值得
It's not worth it.
我们之后再处置她
We'll deal with her later.
杰克 如果你调转机头
Jack, if you turn the plane around,
我可以让病毒传播速度更慢
I can slow this thing down even more.
但在我安全到墨西哥前 我不会给你杀毒码
But I'm not giving you the kill code till I'm safe to Mexico.
发生什么了?
What's going on?
我们回去了
We're going back up.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我只是遵从阿尔梅达不要着陆的命令
I just got orders from Agent Almeida not to land.
他说开回墨西哥
He said to take the plane back to Mexico.
现在着陆
Land the plane now.
我有命令的
I got my orders.
最好别这么想
Don't even think about it.
着陆
Land the plane.
他到底在做什么?
What the hell is he doing?
上尉 飞机发生什么事了?
Lieutenant, what's going on?
为什么飞机转回来了?
Why aren't you turning this plane around?
鲍尔不让我
Bauer won't let me.
什么叫他不让你?
What do you mean he won't let you?
他正用枪指着我
He's got a gun on me.
把我转到扬声器上
Put me on speaker.
杰克 你能听到我吗?
Jack, can you hear me?
是的 我们可以听到 托尼 我们正在洛杉矶降落这架飞机
Yeah, I can hear you, Tony. And we're landing this planein Los Angeles.
我们需要杀毒代码
We need that kill code.
让飞行员掉头
Tell the pilot to turn the plane around right now.
那是上面的命令
That's an order straight from Division.
我们不能总是满足她的要挟
We can't keep giving in to her.
等一分钟
Wait a minute.
我认为我找到了一些东西
I think I'm getting something.
我们不能冒这个险
I can't take that chance.
我们必须阻止这个
We have to stop this thing,
不然很多情报人员将会丧命
or a lot of agents are going to wind up dead.
那么让我们的人阻止这个病毒
Then our people are gonna have to stop it.
我们在努力 我们没有时间了
We're trying. We don't have the time.
把飞机掉头也不能解决问题啊
Turning the plane around is not going to help.
只会让我们离我们应该在的地方越来越远
It's just gonna take us farther away from where we need to be.
-请住嘴托尼  -克萝伊...?
-Chloe...?  -Please shut up, Tony.
道尔顿 转到50号端口
Dalton, bring it back up to 50.
好的
Okay.
-我好了  -我好了发生了什么事?
-I'm clear.  -I'm clear. What branches?
-14到20  -你那边怎么样了道尔顿?
-14 through 20.  -What about you, Dalton?
好的 有效果了 路由器正在恢复正常工作
Yeah, it's working. The routers are coming back up.
我们好了吗?
Are we okay?
我还不确定
I can't tell.
是的 对 对 我们恢复了
Yeah, here, here, it's coming back up.
不 停止! 停止这个程序!
No, stop! Stop the process!
不过它正在执行循环 克萝伊 马上就恢复正常了
But it's cycling through, Chloe. It's almost back up.
这是病毒内建立的一种防御策略
It's a defense ploy built into the worm.
这并不是我们所想象的 这是病毒的后台支撑
It's not what we thought, it's a simple back-prop virus.
我必须找出来源
I have to strip out the resource fork.
不过看看中央处理器 已经差不多100%
But look at the CPU. It's almost 100%.
可恶 亚当 停止 你显示器上看到的只是假象
Damn it, Adam, stop. What you're seeing on the monitor isn't real.
按她说的做
Do what she says.
好的 它停了
All right, it's stopped.
怎么样了?
What's going on?
我认为它在自我重置
I think it's resetting itself.
我们搞定了
We got it.
-在  -杰克?
-Jack?  -Yeah.
-我们搞定了  -完全搞定了?
-We're back up.  -Fully functional?
完全搞定了
Fully functional.
我们继续着陆
We're resuming our approach.
好运
Good work.
你可以给你的长官写一个报告
You can file a report with your commanding officer.
我们所有的系统都已经运转正常了
All our systems are up and running.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
我不在乎你信不信
I don't care what you believe.
确认我们的目录 确认我们没有丢失任何东西
Let's check our directories, make sure we haven't lost anything.
好的 我去做
Yeah, I'm on it.
网络用户呢?
What about the network clients?
依次重置6号代码 直到他们都能连接上
Let's remount those six at a time until they're all on.
好的 看起来问题都解决了 道尔顿 你那边呢?
Okay, these all look good. Dalton, how about yours?
有一些掉线了 不过系统会在10分钟内自我修复的
There's some drop out, but it'll self-adjust in the next ten minutes.
今天做的很好 克萝伊
Great work today, Chloe.
你阻止了一个可能造成严重损失的危机
You averted what could have been a major loss.
我知道
I know.
那杰克和蔡斯马上回来吗?
Are Jack and Chase coming back soon?
-是的  -很好
-Yeah.  -Good.
-你去哪?  -回楼上去
-Where are you going?  -Back upstairs.
不
No.
孩子的事情还没有解决呢
This whole thing with the baby isn't going to just go away.
你的功劳大过你的过失 但是对你的控诉仍旧存在
What you did here will certainly bear well on your case, but the charges still stand.
我们要把你转交给洛杉矶警察 而且不管发生什么事
We're handing you over to LAPD, and no matter what happens,
你必须说出这是谁的孩子
you're going to have to tell them who this baby belongs to.
那人是谁? 他要把安吉拉带到哪里去?
Who's that? Where are they taking Angela?
现在孩子保护服务组织监管她
Child Protective Services has custody of her now.
-噢不不他们不能这么做  -当然可以这么做
-Oh, no, they can't do that.  -Of course they can.
孩子服务组织! 等一下
Child Services! Hold on.
克萝伊 你在做什么?
Chloe, what are you doing?
我会告诉你孩子的父亲是谁
I'll tell you who the father is.
别问我孩子的母亲是谁 我不知道
Don't ask me who the mother is, I don't know.
我只是在帮忙
I was doing a favor.
我发誓我说的是真的
I swear I'm telling the truth.
巴尔布,
Barb
我们打算多留这个孩子一会儿
we're going to hold onto her a little longer.
我们刚刚得到一些新消息
We just got some more information.
为什么你不早说?
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
他不让我对任何人说
He didn't want me to tell anyone.
我只是想对朋友负责
I was trying to be a friend.
对不起
Sorry.
克萝伊,
Chloe
我听说你杀掉了病毒
I heard you stopped the worm.
是的 我做到了
Yeah, I did.
你父亲和蔡斯正在返回洛杉矶 你一定感觉轻松了
Your dad and Chase are back in L.A. You must be relieved.
是的 谢谢
Yes. Thank you.
听着 克萝伊 那个孩子呢?
Look, Chloe, what about the baby?
她怎么了?
What about her?
我认为她们准备指控你
Well, I thought they were pressing charges.
不 那只是个误会
No. That was a misunderstanding.
克萝伊 等等
Chloe, wait.
什么?
What?
那么他们不再指控了?
So they're not pressing charges?
-不  -为什么不?
-No.  -Why not?
额 我准备告诉他们孩子的父亲是谁
Uh, I told them who the father was,
-问题都解决了  -等等问题都解决了?
-and everything's okay.  -Wait, everything's okay?
为什么 谁是孩子的父亲?
Why, who's the father?
蔡斯.
Chase